Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar,
so brother, the topic of today's video is going to be
that brother, you must have
seen it in the thumbnail, many people
request me, many people
comment on me and keep on messaging me and
asking brother, in the comments also many
people keep on asking how you got
selected in IIC Bank, so
friends, in today's video I have
made the video only to tell you how you can get selected
like I have been selected,
how you can get selected in IIC
Bank and brother, in today's video I will
tell you the complete details about myself, brother, how I
searched here, how
I gave the interview and brother, how I got
selected here in ICC Bank,
friends, I am going to tell you the complete information in today's video
because brother, brother, many
people keep asking me,
many people have also commented on me, if you are
new to the channel then friends, you
must subscribe to the channel because brother,
helpful content will keep getting created for you here
and brother, let me tell you one more good news,
if brother  I am
telling you hdfcfund.com that brother, there will be three to
three interviews at your location only.
Whatever location you tell me, I will
schedule three interviews for you at your location,
that too friends, it is free of
cost here. The link is given below,
join the group and brother, send me a
personal message, rest of the friends,
I will schedule your interview at your location itself.
ADAC and also Axis
IDFC are these three to four private banks, in
these, friends, I
know the HR here, I know my personal HR,
and brother, schedule your interview and
go quickly and join here.
WhatsApp is for 2 years. If you want to enter in ICICI Bank
or any other bank, friends, that is, you
want to join, then for that too, friends, it is
mandatory for you to have experience in the banking sector. If
you do not have experience, then brother,
you will have to do sales, that is,
you will have to do a job in any
field, you can have 1 to 2 years of experience.
Get experience and then you can get selected in any bank.
Create your profile on hdfc.com or
linkedin.com, there is an application,
download it and upload your CV there.
Whatever you want, it gets
filtered according to your location.
Friends, apply in it.
Apply 10 to 20 times a day for different
jobs, for different job roles. Keep
trying 10 to 20 times after that.
I have done the same myself. I used to apply
10 to 20 times a day like this.
When I went there, I used to get
calls from HR etc. Now brother,
how did it come to me? Brother, I was on Link as well as on
n.com. Brother, from nukri.com,
brother, I get a call that
brother, you have an interview in ADAC, brother, I
come to Noida and brother, I go to Noida and give the
interview and get selected too.
Brother, I am not able to get a job in HDFC
because there is no  The salary is fixed low
and brother, after that I
meet a friend of mine here from
II Bank, brother I give interview in II Bank,
I get
selected in the first interview, there is no
problem, then my
document verification takes place here,
then the person who is there
comes for verification, in this way brother my
interview gets completed and brother I get
joining in II Bank, brother brother
in II Bank, so friends I had to struggle a lot, it took
me two to three
months while I
was searching and brother to get involved
in this process, I had to wait for two to
three months because right now
I have to remain free for two to three months
without a job, if friends you have
time to come to Noida, then brother
if you can afford then brother you should come to Noida, there are
many jobs here, you
can search like this also or else you do
not need to come, if
you want to work in the private banking sector, any
bank  I have given the link below,
other friends, the link is given below, you can
join the group and go from there and
message me, brother, my
journey was something like this, I got a
job in II Bank by doing this, if you want to get it,
you can also get it, if brother you can make an effort, then
brother you also make an effort, many
people are messaging me that
brother they are 45 or 48, brother only those above 50 can
apply for the job,
otherwise you cannot do it, the
criteria of the banking sector is that from 21 years to
30 years, there is
no problem, it will work till 30 years, it can work till 33 years
also, but brother, if you have
completed your graduation and you have
less than 50 marks, then brother it will
not work at all, do not message me, do not
call me etc. If it is not
possible, if you need a job in other fields, then
brother I can tell you, that is
not a problem brother, if you need a
job  There is a requirement in the private sector, the
link is given below, you can join it
and brother, the mobile number is also given there,
you can also send me a personal message,
brother, I have
searched about the job on two to three platforms
and I have told you as well,
brother, my journey back was very difficult, I
struggled a lot, I
wandered here and there in three to four months, you are getting a
job just by sitting at home, I
am scheduling three interviews for you, the
link is given, you go here and join
and message me,
friends, in today's video, I have told you that
many people asked me
how you got selected, so brother, I got
selected on the basis of interview and brother, I had
a friend who told me, I have his
reference, so friends, I am
also selected here in II Bank, okay, rest
I have told you the entire process, I
hope you liked this information, if you liked the
video then like it, if
brother, even till now you have not subscribed to this channel, then
brother, quickly go and
subscribe to this channel.  See you
next time and till then take care bye